Finding Aid for the Jan Williams Collection of Images, 1962-2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Additional prints, 1988-2001, IV; Item 376-548
  - Jan Williams and four students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-459)
  - Group shot of Jan Williams, Jorge Camiruaga and students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-460)
  - Jan Williams sitting at a desk at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-461)
  - Jan Williams and three students at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-462)
  - Jan Williams and percussionists at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-463)
  - Jan Williams, students, and percussionists at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-464)
  - Jan Williams and students at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-465)
  - Jan Williams, Jorge Camiruaga and students rehearsing for a concert at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-466)
  - Jan Williams, Jorge Camiruaga and students rehearsing for a concert at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-467)
  - Jan Williams, Jorge Camiruaga and students rehearsing for a concert at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-468)
  - Jorge Camiruaga and students rehearsing for a concert at the Universidad de Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-469)
  - Jorge Camiruaga and Jan Williams outdoors in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-470)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Eberhard Blum, and Diane Williams on a bench outdoors in Germany, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-471)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in a courtyard in Rheinsberg, Germany, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-472)
  - Jan Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Eberhard Blum under an arbor in Rheinsberg, Germany, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-473)
  - Eberhard Blum in Rheinsberg, Germany, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-474)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Eberhard Blum, and Diane Williams sitting by the water in Rheinsberg, Germany, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-475)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Ernstalbrecht Stiebler backstage at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-476)
  - Eberhard Blum with Mats Persson and Kristine Scholz, piano duo, at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-477)
  - Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams backstage at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-478)
  - Eberhard Blum and Daniel Seel performing at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-479)
  - Eberhard Blum and Daniel Seel performing at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-480)
  - Eberhard Blum and Daniel Seel performing at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-481)
  - Eberhard Blum and Ann Holyoke Lehmann listening to Daniel Seel at the piano in the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-482)
  - John Patrick Thomas, Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Diane Williams, and Richard Reeve sitting around a table at the Nationalgalerie in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-483)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Diane Williams, in the Blum house, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-484)
  - Eberhard Blum and John Patrick Thomas at a caf in Hackescher Markt in Berlin, 2000-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-485)
  - Michael Svoboda, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum rehearsing for a concert commemorating Eberhard Blum's 60th birthday in Berlin, 2000-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-486)
  - Michael Svoboda, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum rehearsing for a concert commemorating Eberhard Blum's 60th birthday in Berlin, 2000-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-487)
  - Michael Svoboda, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum rehearsing for a concert commemorating Eberhard Blum's 60th birthday in Berlin, 2000-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-488)
  - Stage setup for a concert commemorating Eberhard Blum's 60th birthday in Berlin, 2000-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-489)
  - Close-up of the percussion instruments for a concert commemorating Eberhard Blum's 60th birthday in Berlin, 2000-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-490)
  - Percussion instrument setup at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-491)
  - Percussion instrument setup at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-492)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Ernstalbrecht Stiebler's im Takt at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-493)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Ernstalbrecht Stiebler's im Takt at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-494)
  - Percussion instrument setup at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-495)
  - Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehman, and Jan Williams outside the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-496)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum and unidentified man at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-497)
  - Ernstalbrecht Stiebler and Ann Holyoke Lehmann at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-498)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Lars Petter Hagen at the Edvard Munch House in Warnemünde (Rostock, Germany), 2000-09, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-499)
  - Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams in Fasanenstrasse, Berlin, 2000-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-500)
  - Eberhard Blum rehearsing at the Schauspielhaus, Berlin, 2001-04, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-501)
  - Percussion setup for Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Schauspielhaus, Berlin, 2001-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-502)
  - Stage of the Schauspielhaus shown on monitor backstage, 2001-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-503)
  - Percussion setup for Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Schauspielhaus, Berlin, 2001-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-504)
  - View of stage at the at the Schauspielhaus, Berlin, set for performance of Morton Feldman's King of Denmark, 2001-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-505)
  - Jan Williams setting up percussion instruments for Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Staatsgalerie Stuttgart, 2001, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-506)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Staatsgalerie Stuttgart, 2001, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-507)
  - Percussion setup for Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Staatsgalerie Stuttgart, 2001, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-508)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's King of Denmark at the Staatsgalerie Stuttgart, 2001, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-509)
  - Jan Williams with Joel Chadabe (back to camera), Arna Suttle, Clark Suttle, and Erik Jacobsen at the home of Torben Elmøe after a Sjelland Symphony Orchestra concert, 1990-11, 1 photograph; Elmøe, Torben (Box 4, Item JW-510)
  - John Patrick Thomas, Diane Williams, and Richard Reeve by the water in Hamburg, Germany, 2000, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-511)
  - Jan Williams sitting in front of a statue of Johann Sebastian Bach in Leipzig, 2000, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-512)
  - Jan Williams and John Patrick Thomas standing in front of the water in Lübeck, 2000, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-513)
  - Eberhard Blum, Mrs. Weisman, Adam Weisman, and Jan Williams at Blum's apartment in Berlin, 2000, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-514)
  - Jan Williams and the Perceum Percussion group, 2000, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-515)
  - Jan Williams, Nils Vigeland, Diane Williams, and Yvar Mikashoff, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-516)
  - Jan Williams, and Henrik Svitzer in Copenhagen, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-517)
  - Jan Williams, John Rowland, and Edward Burnham after a school concert in Buffalo, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-518)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing on stage for his solo recital in Århus, Denmark, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-519)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing on stage for his solo recital in Århus, Denmark, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-520)
  - Joel Chadabe in Århus, Denmark, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-521)
  - Jan Williams and Joel Chadabe in Århus, Denmark, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-522)
  - Nils Vigeland, Madeline Burke-Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, Diane Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Hibbard Williams sitting at a table in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-523)
  - Nils Vigeland, Madeline Burke-Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, Diane Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Hibbard Williams sitting at a table in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-524)
  - Hibbard Williams and John Cage in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-525)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, Renée Levine Packer, Hibbard Williams, and John Cage at the New Music America Festival in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-526)
  - Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Diane Williams sitting outside in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-527)
  - Bent Lylloff, Jerzy Zgodzinski, Dave Weckl, and Jan Williams at the home of Bent Lylloff during Williams' induction into the Danish Percussion Society, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-528)
  - Jan Williams with Bent Lyllof during Williams' induction into the Danish Percussion Society at Lyllof's home in Copenhagen, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-529)
  - Bent Lylloff, Jerzy Zgodzinski, Dave Weckl, and Jan Williams at the home of Bent Lylloff during Williams' induction into the Danish Percussion Society, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-530)
  - Jan Williams and Bent Lylloff in Copenhagen, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-531)
  - Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Diane Williams, and Jan Williams in front of a church door in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-532)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum on a bench in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-533)
  - Jan Williams, Diane Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann standing on Unter den Linden with the Brandenburg Gate in the background, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-534)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum by a statue in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-535)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum standing on a pedestal in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-536)
  - Diane Williams, Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann standing on Unter den Linden with the Brandenburg Gate in the background, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-537)
  - Eberhard Blum, Diane Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Jan Williams standing in front of a church door in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-538)
  - Diane Williams, Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann standing in front of a statue in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-539)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum standing on a pedestal in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-540)
  - Eberhard Blum and Diane Williams standing on Unter den Linden with Brandenburg Gate in background, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-541)
  - Diane Williams, Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann standing in front of a statue in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-542)
  - Diane Williams, Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann standing on Unter den Linden with Brandenburg Gate in background, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-543)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum in front of a statue in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-544)
  - Eberhard Blum standing on a pedestal in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-545)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum in front of a statue in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-546)
  - Diane Williams, Eberhard Blum, Martin Riches, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Jan Williams seated at a table in Blum's home in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-547)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, Ann Noël, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Diane Williams, seated at a table in Blum's home in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-548)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Musicians--Photographs; Percussionists--Photographs; Williams, Jan, 1939- --Photographs
Genres
Portraits; Group portraits; Color photographs; Photographs; Color slides
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Jan Williams Collection of Annotated Scores, 1950-1999
Mus. Arc. 10.1
219 scores, most of which have been marked for performance.
Morton Feldman Images by Jan Williams, 1974-1979
Mus. Arc. 2.3
The Morton Feldman Images by Jan Williams date from concert tours made by Morton Feldman and the University at Buffalo's Creative Associates in 1974, 1977, and 1979.